My lords, no formalities.
I've heard much of your country.
Now that I see it,
it truly lives up to its reputation.
At such a young age,
you're already an envoy to the capital.
It speaks to your family's prestige.
Only in the capital
can one witness such splendid performances.
Cheng Qi is the top scholar of Xingyun.
He is the finest poet of our nation.
I hope
his speech tonight
will satisfy you.
Besides the speech,
I heard there are other spectacles.
Of course.
The royal family shares joy with the people,
and specially prepared
a fireworks show for you,
waiting for your appreciation.
Thanks, Your Majesty.
Thanks, Lord Prime Minister.
Brother,
I remember this barrel of gunpowder
wasn't in this spot just now.
It wasn't.
Brother,
check all the barrels of gunpowder again.
The location,
number,
and authenticity
and authenticity.
Don't be too obvious.
Understood.
If there's an issue, follow the plan.
Okay.
My lady,
the royals have entered.
How's it going with Qianzhi?
The fireworks have been moved.
Brother is checking them again.
He'll be back soon.
It'll take about 10 minutes.
Fine.
You have more than 10 minutes.
[They are so sweet.]
[I'm looking forward to the play.]
[I'm so envious.]
[So sweet.]
The mountains and rivers are boundless.
The clouds and the moon are a family.
Yunlang's play
starts now.
[The prosperous Jiangnan is famous for its rivers.]
[Yunjing is a city of talented people.]
[The lights are dazzling.]
[The mood is high.]
[The streets are crowded.]
[It's bustling.]
[Pavilions by the water.]
[Carved balustrades and towers.]
[Music fills the streets.]
[Autumn osmanthus.]
[Peach blossoms for miles.]
[silk brocades in late spring.]
Make sure you have plenty of rouge.
We have guests from the Langyue coming.
We must ensure they leave satisfied.
The stationery set for the young master
is what the distinguished guests love.
It must be a very good business.
[Red flying, green dancing,]
[flowers and brocades everywhere.]
[Good news spreads to every household.]
♪ What are the long robes for ♪
♪ A moment of lingering ♪
♪ Tourists talk ♪
♪ Laughing through life ♪
♪ Ten thousand homes lit with warmth ♪
♪ Peace reigns across the world ♪
Good.
Follow the plan later.
Once I make my move,
you all charge out.
Guest from the Yun State,
This is my best jade hairpin.
Take it back to your wife.
Thank you.
My friend from Yun State,
take a look at my gem.
May you find your beloved,
and seek her across the world.
Next year's Lantern Festival night,
gold hairpins and jade will be in the clouds.
I've heard that the gems from Langyue are rare.
Once the two countries trade,
you should
buy some for your wives.
I've been
planning to make a fur shawl for my wife.
I'm sure it'll be a unique experience
to visit Langyue.
If you come to Langyue,
I'll give you a warm welcome.
Thank you, Princess.
Are you trying to take my good minister away?
That's not gonna happen.
I already have a husband.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
I can
accompany the Grand Preceptor to Langyue.
After all, his mother's family
also has Langyue lineage.
It's like returning home.
Really?
If you have the chance to go to Langyue,
I'll treat you to a feast.
Thank you, Princess.
Your Highness,
this is the daughter of the Grand Preceptor,
the largest merchant in the Yun State.
It's a good opportunity for you to meet her.
When the Yun State's trade delegation visits,
she will likely be among them.
You can establish more connections.
Your Majesty, I'm not in good health,
and have already handed over my family's business.
I'm afraid
I'll let you down.
I wouldn't dare to do business with her.
She wouldn't even let me
read storybooks.
Lord Xiao,
who manages
your fortune?
I can do business with that person.
Lord Xiao,
do I know that person?
Well...
He...
[People gather from afar,]
[jade and pearls fill the market.]
We can talk about business
later.
Don't miss the wonderful performance.
[Flute melodies in the clear sky,]
[water lily songs at night.]
Yes, yes.
[Banners and lanterns line the streets.]
The Emperor's thoughtfulness
has made this the finest banquet.
You live in the bright moon,
far from the hustle and bustle.
You may never have seen
such a grand scene,
that's why you're so excited.
Watch your words.
There are many good things in the bright moon you haven't seen.
When trade opens up,
everyone will see them.
Trade is the trend,
that no one can stop.
Really?
Princess,
the fireworks you like are coming soon.
♪Clouds gathering as the rain stops.♪
♪The Milky Way and the moon are round.♪
♪The moonlight brings longing into the clouds.♪
♪Clouds dance in the wind.♪
♪The moon is coming.♪
Why did you suddenly change the music?
This is specially composed for you.
I want to perform it for you.
Come.
My dear,
look,
who are sitting in there?
Who are they?
They are businessmen and common people from the Yun State.
I see them.
My parents are there, too.
And over there,
they are from the Langyue State.
That's great.
Now,
Yun and Yue are in close contact.
If I want to
buy you a jade hairpin again,
I don't have to go so far away.
♪Thinking back to our first encounter,♪
♪how many coincidences led us there.♪
♪Hairpins and golden hairpins carry our secret messages,♪
♪binding my life to yours, never to fail you.♪
So pretty.
Look at that one.
That color is also pretty.
Grand Preceptor,
you seem a bit confused.
It's so beautiful.
Is the speech you received from the Imperial Study
not like this?
This is just so beautiful.
How wonderful!
Sincere,
and warm.
Just like their love,
It's like the picture of a couple
in a million families.
We are like the mountains and rivers,
clouds and moon,
the heaven and earth,
and the crowd.
My dear,
this is my love for you.
I love you
in the same way.
It's so beautiful.
If you like it,
I'll give you a better one.
I'm talking about their love.
I can give you that too.
The princess and the emperor's son-in-law
are indeed a loving couple.
Zhang Xi Yun
The fireworks were originally placed in the palace.
Why are they outside?
I thought
I would have to break my promise to the princess.
Your Majesty,
it was my father's idea.
Shut up.
My father was worried that the fireworks
would endanger you and Princess.
So he ordered me to put them outside.
You are indeed thoughtful.
No wonder the Grand Preceptor
entrusted his life
to you.
You flatter me.
Your Majesty,
I want them to perform again at Langyue.
And take the fireworks with them.
Don't be so hasty, Princess.
I have to reward them first.
Go to hell!
Guard the Emperor!
The Su's Escort Agency, take your positions!
Evacuate the people in an orderly manner!
Don't panic!
Go!
The Yun people are indeed unreliable.
I guess he wanted to say
you're unreliable.
Protect me!
Zhang Wuheng,
do you want to rebel?
So what?
My lady,
go save the emperor.
Don't worry about me.
I can protect myself.
Just fight!
Don't move!
Or I'll kill him!
Su Yuejiao,
Cheng Qi's life is in my hands.
You have two choices now.
Either
you kill the official,
or
kill your husband.
I'll count to three.
Make your choice.
Three.
Mr. Su,
you can't kill the official.
Two.
My lady,
remember our agreement.
If you don't act,
I will.
Mr. Su.
Qijia!
Shoot!
Zhang Wuheng,
I've treated you well.
Since I took the throne,
you've risen rapidly.
Why would you
plot against me?
You've also harmed Langyue
and killed my general!
The winner takes all.
Why bother with words?
Take him away.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
Zhang Wuheng's daughter, Zhang Xiyun,
has been using
the Star Conference
and the bookshops
to win people over,
while using business as a cover
to amass wealth for Zhang Wuheng.
Please punish her.
The stolen silver from Langyue
was transported from your shop.
The bribes for officials
were handled by your people.
And the explosives for the play
were delivered by you, if I remember correctly.
Please punish me.
Cheng Qi and Su Yuejiao, for their service,
They are awarded with
10,000 taels of silver,
four treasures of the study,
a mansion, and a royal pen.
Miss Su,
what else
do you want?
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But I would like to
trade the rewards
for Zhang Xi's life.
I hope Your Majesty can grant my request.
Didn't she
fight you for Cheng Qi
and almost ruin the Escort Agency?
Why do you plead for her?
Your Majesty knows even this little thing.
I've been following your every move.
Of course I know.
My mother taught me
to be a hero
and forgive the enemy.
Although I don't like her,
she did help us this time,
and saved the official.
If the official killed her,
it would damage the relationship.
Please
show mercy.
Your Majesty,
Zhang Xi Yun
did have a rift with our escort agency before,
but
she didn't take lives.
It can be seen that she is different
from her father and brother.
And it was all Zhang Xi Yun
who mediated
the explosives matter,
so that the performance can be held smoothly.
I think
she may
not be involved in this matter.
I hope Your Majesty can investigate clearly.
Rise, all of you.
Rise.
Since she has repented,
and you all plead for her,
it's not impossible
to spare her.
But then, your rewards will be forfeit.
No regrets allowed.
We, as a couple,
should contribute to the empire.
We don't seek any reward.
Then confiscate the property of the Zhang family
and deal with it separately.
As for the rest,
let bygones be bygones.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But there's a reward
that has nothing to do with the bounty.
I wonder
if Su
would still refuse it?
Your Majesty,
I don't want anything in return.
Then the title of the best agency
in the country is still unknown.
Your Majesty, wait.
You see,
it's not easy to
be a live-in son-in-law.
If I get this reward,
I'll
be more confident.
I hereby
bestow the title of
the No.1 Escort Agency in the Yun State
to the Su's Agency.
It will be the official and royal agency.
Cheng Qi.
Will "Matrilocal Life"
be updated?
It depends on
whether my wife allows it.
I remember you two
haven't had a real wedding ceremony.
Bestow the concentric jade.
Never be separated.
Choose a day for the wedding.
Print ten thousand copies of the book.
Announce it to the whole country.
I will never forget
the great kindness of the emperor.
That's great.
In this way,
we can renew it forever, right?
Jiaojiao,
when you visit your parents-in-law,
be polite and do more chores.
Don't worry, Grandpa.
Cheng Qi,
she's getting better at drinking.
It might not work anymore.
You need to make the atmosphere lively.
That's how I'll become a great-grandfather.
Don't worry, Grandpa.
I'm even more eager than you.
Take good care of Grandpa.
I'll bring you some Ning'an specialties.
You must bring my books.
I'll bring you Zhuangyuan cookies.
Grandpa, Uncle.
It's getting late.
We should set off now.
Okay.
We're leaving.
Gong Xi,
isn't it amazing?
Last time we went to Ning'an,
My Lord pretended to get married,
but he got a real son-in-law.
You were so unlucky at that time,
saying My Lord would meet bandits.
As a result, he was robbed by two groups of people.
No way.
You're the one who's jinxing this time.
My Lord.
My son-in-law.
There are a few bandits ahead.
You guys stay here.
We'll deal with them.
Bandits?
Jiao, this...
What should we do?
Don't worry.
Leave them to them.
It's okay.
The No.1 Escort Agency of Yun State
is passing through your place today.
I'm Su Yueqi.
Please
give us a favor.
The No.1 Escort Agency of Yun State?
I think you made up the name.
How dare you insult the escort agency?
Why does he look so familiar?
My lady.
Su's Escort Agency.
We will protect the goods at all costs.
Excuse me,
are you here for money
or for my life?
We just want to make a living.
Why would we kill you?
This young lady is quite pretty.
How about...
What are you doing?
Be professional.
Don't give yourself away.
Are we acting?
This is too lame.
Just play along.
Since you're after money,
I have a treasure
that's priceless.
It's a coincidence to meet you four.
I'm willing to
give it to you.
It's a gift from a friend.
It's priceless.
You can sell it
to support yourselves
for several years.
If it was given by your friend,
why do you treat it so casually?
You don't know,
gentlemen.
This friend of mine
is illiterate
and has a bad temper.
ignorant,
and reckless.
I heard
he's even taken to banditry lately.
I'm sure you all know him.
What do you think, my lady?
Boring.
When did you figure it out?
You two are so slim,
and Zhalu is so bulky,
who wouldn't notice?
How did you get here?
We were heading to Klak City to see the new shop.
We heard you were getting married in Ning'an,
so we hurried over to congratulate you.
Congratulations.
You have no idea
how capable Xi Yun is.
With her help,
I can make a fortune in any business.
But,
why didn't you tell us about your wedding?
What do you mean?
It's too far.
I don't want to bother you to come here.
By the way,
after our wedding,
the escort agency will start to
deliver official goods from Yun State to Langyue.
I hope you can
give us a hand.
Then you have to promise me
that I'll be the first to read your new scripts.
Did you hear that?
Can you do that?
I'll do everything as you wish.
You should learn from him.
Why don't you learn from him?
I...
Can you learn from him?
Learn from him.
Alright, alright.
You good-for-nothing.
It's time.
The newlyweds will serve tea to their parents.
Good.
Dad, please have the tea.
Okay.
Mom, please have the tea.
Good daughter, good daughter-in-law.
Is the tea good, Lord Cheng?
Of course.
My children,
today is the wedding day of my son.
How can I not be happy?
Qi,
I've never
been so happy as today.
In the world,
everything is like dust,
only you are the pearl in my heart,
in my bones,
in my blood,
and I can't bear to part with you.
From now on,
your joy is my joy,
your sorrow is my sorrow.
I'll do everything I can
to make you smile.
Thank you for your nurturing
and education.
I will be filial to you in the future.
Did you understand?
No.
But I'm so touched.
Alright, alright.
Come into my arms.
Come on, get up.
The wedding is complete.
Send them to the bridal chamber.
Good.
Hurry, let's go to the bridal chamber.
Honey,
you did well today.
I was more nervous than in battle.
Luckily,
I memorized everything.
If I were a civil official,
Yue Shangzhi wouldn't stand a chance.
Come, drink this cup of wine.
May your love last forever.
May you have a son soon.
The lock of unity never breaks.
And this one.
Safe and sound.
Bite it.
Bite it. There's more.
Bite it. Bite it.
They tease me for not knowing sayings.
Adding flowers to brocade.
A wedding night moment is worth gold.
Let's go.
Go. A wedding night moment is priceless.
May you have a baby soon.
May you be happy together forever.
May you be harmonious and beautiful.
May you be together forever.
Let's go.
My dear,
do you remember this room?
Of course.
Last time, it was here
that you tricked me into getting on the ship.
It all
seems like a dream.
Yeah.
It seems like nothing
has changed,
but everything has changed.
My dear,
thank you for giving me such a beautiful dream.
You
made my dream come true.
You are my dream wife.